[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the lightest element that is a metal?", "correct_answer": "Lithium", "incorrect_answers": ["Titanium", "Cobalt", "Boron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He reigned until 1725 and carried out a policy of Westernization and expansion, that transformed his country into a major European power.", "correct_answer": "Peter the Great", "incorrect_answers": ["Augustus II of Poland", "Kemal Ataturk", "Frederich the Great"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which fossil was proved to be a hoax?", "correct_answer": "Piltdown Man", "incorrect_answers": ["Cro-Magnon Man", "Neanderthal Man", "Kennewick Man"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these names refers to the Candlenut tree, also known as Candleberry and Kemiri?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Indian walnut", "Kukui nut tree", "Varnish tree"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the villains evil goal in the motion picture, Goldfinger?", "correct_answer": "Make Fort Knoxs gold reserve radioactive", "incorrect_answers": ["Kill James Bond", "Steal the plans of a new weapons system", "Brainwash the head of the Secret Service"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these elements has the highest melting point?", "correct_answer": "Carbon", "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Hydrogen", "Oxygen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the color of the Dont Walk pedestrian crossing signal in Canada and the United States?", "correct_answer": "Portland Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["Puce", "Coral red", "Scarlet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the industrial name for popcorn kernels that fail to pop?", "correct_answer": "Old maids", "incorrect_answers": ["Spinsters", "Barrens", "Bachelors"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first Major League Baseball manager to win a World Series in both the National and American Leagues.", "correct_answer": "Sparky Anderson", "incorrect_answers": ["John McGraw", "Jim Leyland", "Joe Torre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie 2001 Maniacs begins with college friends Anderson Lee, Cory Jones and Nelson Elliot traveling south for Spring Break. Where were they heading?", "correct_answer": "Daytona Beach", "incorrect_answers": ["Savannah", "Miami", "New Orleans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many people are killed in the movie The Wild Bunch?", "correct_answer": "145", "incorrect_answers": ["45", "345", "245"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the New Zealand-born director of the Academy Award-nominated movie North Country?", "correct_answer": "Nikki Caro", "incorrect_answers": ["Marleen Gorris", "Julie Dash", "Josee Dayan"]}]